I ain't tryna
Ain't tryna be cool like you
Wobblin' around in your high heel shoes
I'm clumsy, made friends with the floor
Two for one, you know a bitch buy four
And two left feet, you know I always drop
First thing a girl did was a bop
I'm the whole damn cake and the cherry on top
Shook up the bottle, made a good girl pop
You ain't even here to party
Ken in the club tryna pipe a Barbie
I don't wanna go, go, go with the flow
Back bend 'til I touch my toes
I don't wanna row, row, row the boat
Wrist full of rocks and I hope I float
Big up yourself 'cause you know they don't
I chew, chew, chew 'cause they hope I choke
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss I'ma shine like gloss
Said, bitch, I'm the after you been the before
I been a stallion, you been a sea horse
Don't need a report, don't need a press run
All of my bad pics been all my best ones
I wear the hat and I wear the pants
I am advanced so I get advance
And I do my dance and cancel the plans
Said, boo, don't be mad 'cause you had a chance
sSid, I took it and I ran for it
I run it, then I stand on it
Money on the floor when we dance on it
Shine bright, let them put a tan on it
Said, I took it and I ran for it
I run it, then I stand on it
Money on the floor when we dance on it
Shine bright, let them put a tan on it like
Bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
Bitch, I'm a bitch
I'm a boss, I'm a boss
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss
I'm a bitch
I'm a boss
I'm a bitch and a boss, I'ma shine like gloss